Inventory of the Paul B. Ryan papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- First Line of Defense Research Materials File, 1882-1986
  - US Navy (USN) issues, 1959, 1962-1981
    - Vessels and weaponry, 1962-1981
      - Naval aviation documents, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Naval ship gap, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Navy's 5-year shipbuilding plan, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - New weaponry, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - New York Times index on USN building programs, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - SECNAV (former) Middendorf, naval shipbuilding, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Systems analysis, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - US naval air power, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - US shipbuilding and industrial gap, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - USN shipbuilding and ships, 1962-1965 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam War materials, 1945, 1965-1978, 1982
    - French Indochina documents, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - General Westmoreland on Vietnam War, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Hanoi bombings and POWs, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - JFK's order to McNamara-Gilpatric on Vietnam, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - "Logistic History of Vietnam War," Edwin Hooper, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - McNamara on funding the Vietnam War, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - National United Front for the Liberation of Vietnam, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Senate investigation of Vietnam air war, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Vietnam Conflict map, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam War, 1969-1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - World War II, 1943-1945, 1963-1969, 1984
    - Court inquiry on Pearl Harbor attack, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
    - Documents on WWII Japanese sub I-400, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Information on Pearl Harbor attacks, 1963-1969 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Japanese submarine I-400, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - WWII memoir by US Navy officer, 1943-1945 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- The Iranian Rescue Mission Research Materials File, 1978-1981, 1985
  - Chronology of events in Middle East 1945-1980, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Iran, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Iran crisis, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Iran hostage crisis research materials, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
  - Iran hostage rescue mission, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - The Iranian Rescue Mission: Why It Failed, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, publicity, and reviews related to Ryan's book.
  - Middle East crisis, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Photographs, 1925, 1941-1985
  - Aircraft carriers and submarines photographs and printed material, 1941-1985 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Desert One crash and failed Iranian hostage rescue, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Desert One maps and negatives, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Desert One photographs and maps, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Desert One photographs and maps, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Diego Garcia Navy Base, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - First Line of Defense, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Ho Chi Minh, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Iran hostage crisis photographs and slides, 1976-1981 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper photographs of Panama Canal and treaty signing, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Odenwald capture, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Panama Canal and U.S.-Panama relations, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Photographs, 1976-1980 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, news, and maps of Panama, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - SECNAV John Chaffee, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - SECNAV Lehman, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Turkey, ships, officers, 1925 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - US Navy, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - US Navy, 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - US Navy and naval weapons systems, 1975-1980 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - US Navy ships, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Oversize Material, undated (Map-case , Folder 1)